Mommy.
แม่คะ
Don't let go of my hand, Mommy.
อย่าปล่อยมือหนูนะคะแม่
Mommy!
แม่
The man… He was a Czechoslovakian of German ancestry.
ผู้ชาย… เป็นชาวเชโกสโลวาเกีย เชื้อสายเยอรมัน
He was the eldest son of a family who remained in Bohemia
เขาเป็นลูกชายคนโตของครอบครัว ที่ยังอยู่ในโบฮีเมีย
after World War Two.
หลังสงครามโลกครั้งที่สอง
He was a soldier who graduated from a military academy.
เขาเป็นทหารที่จบจากโรงเรียนทหาร
He was a member of the elite who would lead his country to the future.
เขาเป็นสมาชิกของชนชั้นสูง ที่จะนำประเทศนี้ไปสู่อนาคต
His name…
ชื่อของเขาคือ…
That does not matter.
เรื่องนั้นไม่สำคัญหรอก
The woman…
ผู้หญิง…
She was the only daughter of elementary school teachers in Moravia.
เธอเป็นลูกสาวคนเดียว ของครูโรงเรียนประถมในโมราเวีย
She was a beautiful woman with blonde hair and blue eyes.
เธอเป็นผู้หญิงสวย ผมบลอนด์และตาสีฟ้า
She entered Brno University and majored in genetic engineering.
เธอเข้ามหาวิทยาลัยเบอร์โน และเรียนเอกพันธุวิศวกรรม
Her professors said she was talented and had a bright future.
อาจารย์ของเธอบอกว่า เธอมีพรสวรรค์และมีอนาคตที่สดใส
Her name…
ชื่อของเธอ…
does not matter.
ไม่สำคัญหรอก
The two of them met at a cafe in Prague.
พวกเขาสองคนเจอกันที่ร้านกาแฟในปราก
It didn't take long before they fell in love.
ไม่นานพวกเขาก็ตกหลุมรักกัน
Before long, the woman became pregnant.
แล้วไม่นานผู้หญิงคนนั้นก็ตั้งท้อง
Then the man told her…
แล้วผู้ชายก็บอกเธอว่า
"I was assigned to do this."
"ผมได้รับมอบหมายให้ทำแบบนี้
"Men and women have been chosen based on their race, intelligence,
"ผู้ชายและผู้หญิงถูกเลือกจากเชื้อชาติ สติปัญญา
physical features, and athletic ability to have children together."
ลักษณะทางกายภาพ และความสามารถด้านกีฬาเพื่อมีลูกด้วยกัน
"It is an experiment being done with several dozen couples."
มันเป็นการทดลองที่ทำกับคู่รักหลายคู่
"We are one of those couples in this experiment."
เราเป็นหนึ่งในคู่รักในการทดลองนี้"
The man carried out his assignment according to the plan.
ผู้ชายทำงานที่ได้รับมอบหมายตามแผน
He told her that he now had no intention of following it.
เขาบอกเธอว่าตอนนี้เขาไม่คิดจะทำตามแผนแล้ว
Then he said…
แล้วเขาก็พูดว่า…
Let's run away!
หนีกันเถอะ
The two of them ran away.
พวกเขาสองคนหนีไป
The man declared that he wouldn't follow their plan.
ผู้ชายยืนยันว่าเขาจะไม่ทำตามแผนของพวกเขา
But his actions were already figured into the plan.
แต่การกระทำของเขา ถูกรวมไว้ในแผนการอยู่แล้ว
The woman was confined in an unfamiliar room.
ผู้หญิงคนนั้นถูกขังไว้ในห้องที่ไม่คุ้นเคย
Let me see him.
ขอฉันเจอเขาหน่อยเถอะ
He's been given a new assignment.
เขาได้รับมอบหมายงานใหม่แล้วละ
She said,
เธอบอกว่า
"Let me see him."
"ขอฉันเจอเขาหน่อยเถอะ"
But she knew
แต่เธอก็รู้
that he was already no longer alive.
ว่าเขาไม่มีชีวิตอยู่แล้ว
The children she carried developed normally.
เด็กที่อยู่ในท้องเธอเติบโตตามปกติ
She was carrying twins.
เธออุ้มท้องลูกแฝด
Look this way.
มองทางนี้หน่อย
She began to realize…
เธอเริ่มรู้ตัว…
that this man who often visited…
ว่าผู้ชายที่มาเยี่ยมบ่อยๆ…
and who sketched pictures of her…
และเป็นคนสเก็ตช์รูปเธอ…
that this man was the one who had masterminded this experiment.
ชายคนนี้เป็นหนึ่งในผู้ริเริ่มการทดลองนี้
I won't forgive this.
ฉันจะไม่ยกโทษให้
I will never forgive you.
ฉันจะไม่มีวันยกโทษให้แก
Even if I die,
ต่อให้ฉันตาย
the children growing inside me,
แต่เด็กๆ ที่เติบโตในตัวฉัน
I swear they will take vengeance on you.
ฉันสาบานเลยว่าพวกเขาจะไปแก้แค้นแกแน่
You say the most amusing things.
คุณพูดสิ่งที่ตลกที่สุด
She came due and started going into labor.
แล้วเธอก็ถึงกำหนดคลอด และเริ่มเจ็บท้องคลอดลูก
She was moved to a different room to ease the labor pains.
เธอถูกย้ายไปห้องอื่น เพื่อลดความเจ็บปวดจากการคลอด
That's when she took action.
นั่นคือตอนที่เธอลงมือ
Though the air vent was only
แม้ว่าช่องระบายอากาศ
a couple dozen centimeters wide, she dragged her heavy body
จะกว้างแค่ไม่กี่สิบเซนติเมตร แต่เธอก็ลากร่างกายหนักๆ ของเธอ
wracked by labor pains through it to escape.
ที่ทรุดโทรมเพราะปวดท้องคลอดลูก ผ่านช่องนั้นเพื่อหลบหนี
She collapsed on the road a few dozen meters from the front gate.
เธอล้มลงบนถนน ห่างจากประตูหน้าไม่กี่สิบเมตร
Her water was already broken.
ถุงน้ำคร่ำของเธอแตกแล้ว
How beautiful.
น่ารักจริงๆ
Such beautiful children.
เด็กๆ น่ารักจริงๆ
So, these are the children that will lead the future of humanity.
เด็กพวกนี้คือคนที่จะเป็นผู้นำมนุษยชาติใช่ไหมครับ
They're magnificent.
พวกเขาวิเศษมากเลย
I thought of names for them.
ฉันตั้งชื่อไว้ให้พวกเขาแล้ว
Don't bother yourself with such pointless matters.
อย่าลำบากกับเรื่องไร้สาระแบบนั้นเลย
I have thought of names for the babies.
ฉันตั้งชื่อไว้ให้เด็กๆ แล้ว
You don't need to do that.
คุณไม่จำเป็นต้องทำแบบนั้นหรอก
Give them names.
ตั้งชื่อให้พวกเขาเถอะนะ
Give those children names!
ตั้งชื่อเด็กพวกนั้นด้วย
You must!
คุณต้องทำนะ
Forget it.
ช่างมันเถอะ
They don't need names.
พวกเขาไม่ต้องมีชื่อหรอก
Franz Bonaparta…
ฟรานซ์ โบนาปาร์ตา…
That's right.
ใช่แล้ว
Johan asked me where he is.
โยฮันถามฉันว่าเขาอยู่ไหน
Do you mean Bonaparta lives?
หมายความว่าโบนาปาร์ตายังมีชีวิตอยู่เหรอ
"I won't forgive this."
"ฉันจะไม่ยกโทษให้
"I will never forgive you."
ฉันจะไม่มีวันยกโทษให้แก
"Even if I die,
ต่อให้ฉันตาย
the children growing inside me,
แต่เด็กๆ ที่เติบโตในตัวฉัน
I swear they will take vengeance on you."
ฉันสาบานเลยว่าพวกเขาจะไปแก้แค้นแกแน่"
Franz Bonaparta lives, doesn't he?
ฟรานซ์ โบนาปาร์ตายังมีชีวิตอยู่ใช่ไหม
Ask Johan.
ถามโยฮันสิ
He is here.
เขาอยู่ที่นี่
You're one hell of a doctor.
คุณเป็นหมอที่ห่วยแตกจริงๆ
There's a hospital up ahead.
ข้างหน้ามีโรงพยาบาล
I'll take you there if you tell me where Johan is.
ฉันจะพานายไปที่นั่นถ้านายบอกว่าโยฮันอยู่ไหน
If you don't go, you'll die from blood loss.
ถ้านายไม่ไปโรงพยาบาล นายจะเสียเลือดจนตาย
I… don't know what I don't know.
ฉัน… ฉันไม่รู้สิ่งที่ฉันไม่รู้
Hurry up and tell us!
รีบบอกเรามาซะ
You're one hell of a doctor.
คุณเป็นหมอที่ห่วยแตกจริงๆ
Not only did you shoot me,
นอกจากจะยิงผมแล้ว
you let me bleed like this then proceed to blackmail me.
ยังปล่อยให้ผมเลือดออกแบบนี้แล้วก็ข่มขู่ผมอีก
Where is Johan?
โยฮันอยู่ไหน
You're one hell of a doctor.
คุณเป็นหมอที่ห่วยแตกจริงๆ
Hurry up and tell us! Now!
รีบๆ บอกเรามาซะ บอกมา!
I don't know what I don't know.
ผมไม่รู้สิ่งที่ผมไม่รู้
Eva.
เอวา
There's a payphone over there.
มีตู้โทรศัพท์อยู่ตรงนั้น
Call the hospital and tell them that a man bleeding in this car.
โทรไปที่โรงพยาบาลแล้วบอกพวกเขาว่า มีผู้ชายเลือดออกอยู่ในรถคันนี้
Are you insane?
จะบ้ารึไง
He's about to tell us--
เขากำลังจะบอกเรา…
If we wait any longer, he could die.
ถ้ารอนานกว่านี้ เขาอาจตายได้
Hurry up and call.
เร็วเข้า รีบไปโทรเถอะ
You've saved a life again.
คุณช่วยชีวิตคนอีกแล้ว
You always end up doing this.
สุดท้ายคุณก็ทำแบบนี้ตลอด
You can't kill anyone.
คุณฆ่าใครไม่ได้
He's been wanting to see you.
เขาอยากเจอคุณมาตลอด
So I'll tell you… where Johan is.
เพราะฉะนั้นผมจะบอกคุณ… ว่าโยฮันอยู่ไหน
Kenzo, an ambulance from the hospital will be here soon.
เคนโซ เดี๋ยวรถพยาบาล จากโรงพยาบาลก็มาแล้ว
We need to get out of--
เราต้องออกไปจาก…
Where's Kenzo?
เคนโซอยู่ไหน
He left.
เขาไปแล้ว
He left a message for you.
เขาฝากบอกคุณว่า
"I can't let you get any more involved than you already are."
"ผมยอมให้คุณมีส่วนเกี่ยวข้อง มากไปกว่านี้ไม่ได้แล้ว
"I ruined your life."
ผมทำลายชีวิตคุณมากพอแล้ว
"I'm very sorry for that. I hope you find happiness."
ผมขอโทษจริงๆ หวังว่าคุณจะพบความสุขนะ"
Why are you crying?
ร้องไห้ทำไม
I can't understand it.
ผมไม่เข้าใจ
It makes no sense to me at all.
ผมว่ามันไม่สมเหตุสมผลเลย
Johan.
โยฮัน
THREE FROGS
(กบสามตัว)
NAMELESS MONSTER
(ปีศาจไร้ชื่อ)
Welcome back.
ยินดีต้อนรับกลับมา
Fire!
ไฟไหม้!
The Three Frogs is burning!
กบสามตัวไฟไหม้!
Go on. Eat up.
เอาเลย กินซะ
It will get caught in your throat if you eat so quickly.
อย่ารีบกินเกินไป ระวังจะติดคอนะ
You must be awfully hungry.
พวกเธอคงหิวมากเลยสินะ
So, where are you two from?
แล้วพวกเธอสองคนมากจากไหนกันล่ะ
What are your names?
ชื่ออะไรกันจ๊ะ
They don't want to talk at all.
พวกเขาไม่อยากพูดกันเลยนะเนี่ย
That's okay. You can talk once you've eaten your fill.
ไม่เป็นไร กินให้อิ่มแล้วค่อยพูดก็ได้
Wait up!
รอด้วย
-Wait for me! -Over here!
- รอฉันด้วย - ทางนี้
What will we do?
เราจะทำยังไงกันดี
What do you mean?
หมายความว่ายังไง
Don't you think those children have parents somewhere?
คุณไม่คิดเหรอว่า เด็กพวกนั้นมีพ่อแม่อยู่ที่ไหนสักแห่ง
Even if they do, they must have a reason for not going back.
ถ้ามี พวกเขาก็คงมีเหตุผลที่จะไม่กลับไปหา
You and I…
คุณกับฉัน…
We always wanted children.
เราอยากมีลูกกันมาตลอด
That's true.
ก็จริง
Why don't we adopt--
ทำไมเราไม่รับ…
Don't be ridiculous!
อย่าไร้สาระน่ะ
I'm sorry for getting angry.
ผมขอโทษที่โมโหนะ
We should call the police.
เราควรโทรแจ้งตำรวจนะ
What's wrong, little boy?
เป็นอะไรไปจ๊ะ หนุ่มน้อย
Look at these! Aren't they pretty flowers?
ดูนี่สิ ดอกไม้สวยเนอะ
I'll give them to the old man and woman.
ฉันจะเอาไปให้คุณลุงกับคุณป้า
You don't need to.
ไม่ต้องหรอก
Why?
ทำไมล่ะ
Remember what I said?
จำที่ฉันบอกได้ไหม
I've got a good plan.
ฉันมีแผนที่ดีแล้ว
Come on.
ไปกันเถอะ
Oh darn you!
นิสัยไม่ดี!
Wait up!
รอด้วย!
Wait! Come on!
รอด้วย! รอด้วยสิ!
At last, we meet.
ในที่สุดเราก็ได้พบกัน
When I escaped from the Red Rose Mansion
ตอนที่ฉันหนีออกมาจากคฤหาสน์กุหลาบแดง
and arrived at our place at the Three Frogs…
และกลับไปถึงบ้านของเราที่กบสามตัว…
you welcomed me back.
เธอต้อนรับที่ฉันกลับไป
So this time it's my turn to say it to you.
คราวนี้ถึงตาฉันพูดกับเธอบ้างนะ
Welcome back.
ยินดีต้อนรับกลับมา
A lot of time has passed…
เวลาผ่านไปมากแล้ว…
since I came to get you in Heidelberg on your 20th birthday.
ตั้งแต่ฉันมารับเธอที่ไฮเดิลแบร์ค ในวันเกิดครบ 20 ปีของเธอ
"Came to get me"?
"มารับฉัน" เหรอ
You came to kill me!
มาฆ่าฉันซะมากกว่า!
You killed the Fortners and the Lieberts…
นายฆ่าครอบครัวฟอร์ตเนอร์และครอบครัวลีแบร์ท
and everyone that's ever been kind to us.
และทุกคนที่เคยดีกับเรา
You… killed all of them!
นาย… นายฆ่าพวกเขาทุกคน!
You must live!
คุณต้องรอดสิ
What?
หา
I just said the weather sure is nice today.
เมื่อกี้ผมบอกว่าวันนี้อากาศดีมากน่ะ
Yes, it is.
อ๋อ ครับ
Driver.
โชเฟอร์ครับ
Yes?
ครับ
Can you please drive a little faster?
ช่วยขับเร็วกว่านี้หน่อยได้ไหมครับ
OPERATION ROOM 3
(ห้องผ่าตัดสาม)
It will be fine. Hang in there.
ไม่เป็นไรนะ อดทนไว้
Shoot me.
ยิงฉันสิ
Kill him…
ฆ่าเขา…
I'll save you.
ฉันจะช่วยนายเอง
Will you shoot me like you did before?
เธอจะยิงฉันเหมือนที่เคยทำรึเปล่า
Yes.
ใช่
And that'll be the end of this.
แล้วเรื่องนี้จะได้ถึงจุดจบซะที
The end…
จุดจบ…
What is the end?
จุดจบคืออะไร
Many, many times I have seen the end.
ฉันเคยเห็นจุดจบมามากมายหลายครั้ง
This is the end!
นี่ไงจุดจบ
You will die, and so will I.
นายจะตาย และฉันก็จะตายด้วย
You've seen it?
นายเคยเห็นเหรอ
What have you seen?
นายเห็นอะไร
What is it you've seen?
นายเห็นอะไรบ้าง
You don't know.
นายไม่รู้หรอก
I will tell you…
ฉันจะเล่า…
the truly horrifying story.
เรื่องสยองที่แท้จริงให้นายฟังเอง
I'm back.
ฉันกลับมาแล้ว